<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>DLCNukaWorld</Addon>
    <Source>en</Source>
    <Dest>cs</Dest>
    <Version>2</Version>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2" sID="00134C">
      <EDID>[0101F20E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Yeah, man. Yeah! Hell yeah! You don't have to come up to me and say "Man, RedEye, that was so good... man, I loved that." I already know it's good, I don't need your approval.</Source>
      <Dest>Jo, lidi. Jo! Sakra jo! Nemusíte přijít a říkat: „Člověče, Spojivko, to bylo tak dobrý... chlape, já to miluju.“ Já už dávno vím, že je to dobrý a nepotřebuju vaše ujištění.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001374">
      <EDID>[0101F205]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>This here is a song I wrote totally by myself, without any help at all.</Source>
      <Dest>Tohle je písnička, kterou jsem napsal úplně sám, bez jakékoliv pomoci.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0013E3">
      <EDID>[0101F1F5]</EDID>
      <REC id="0">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I ain't gonna lie to you all - love hurts. It really does.</Source>
      <Dest>Nebudu vám všem lhát - láska ubližuje. Opravdu to tak je.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00140B">
      <EDID>[0101F207]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001439">
      <EDID>[0101F206]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>This next one, I been hearin' some shit that I ripped this off or whatever. That's bullshit, man. Ain't true. I wrote this. Swear it.</Source>
      <Dest>A další, o které jsem slyšel kecy, že jsem ji někde ukrad nebo co. To je blbost, lidi. Není to pravda. Já jsem to napsal. Přísahám.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0014AC">
      <EDID>[0101F200]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>A "RedEye original", you could say.</Source>
      <Dest>„Spojivkův originál“ dalo by se říct.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0014D0">
      <EDID>[010201D1]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Listen up, all you Disciples, Operators, Pack... guys, and whoever the hell else is out there these days!</Source>
      <Dest>Poslouchejte všichni... lidi od Stoupenců, Provozáků, Smečky a kdokoliv další, kdo tady ještě je!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0014E0">
      <EDID>[010201CB]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Add the Galactic Zone to the Overboss' conquests. Yeah!</Source>
      <Dest>Přidejte si Galaktickou zónu na seznam superšéfova dobytýho území. Jo!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0014E2">
      <EDID>[010201C4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>And the Overboss has decided to leave the Galactic Zone in the hands of...</Source>
      <Dest>A superšéf se rozhodl nechat Galaktickou zónu v rukách...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0014EA">
      <EDID>[010201C6]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>But hey, after a year of accomplishing jack shit, this sure is one hell of a step in the right direction!</Source>
      <Dest>Ale víte co, po roce dosáhnutí úplnýho prdu, je tohle rozhodně krok správným směrem!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0014F2">
      <EDID>[010201CD]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>In case you haven't heard, the Overboss has cleared out Dry Rock Gulch, and it is all ours!</Source>
      <Dest>Jestli jste to neslyšeli, superšéf vyčistil Vyprahlou rokli a je celá naše!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001507">
      <EDID>[010201C7]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Add another one to the tally, deadbeats. The Overboss is getting shit DONE!</Source>
      <Dest>Přidejte další bod do scóre, flákači. Superšéf opravdu maká!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001508">
      <EDID>[010201C9]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Listen up, all you junkies, low-lives, and all-around assholes! We've got a reason to celebrate!</Source>
      <Dest>Poslouchejte vy všichni feťáci, ubožáci a celkově blbouni. Máme důvod oslavovat!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001516">
      <EDID>[010201D4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Pack! Means a whole new section of Nuka-World will smell like a brahmin pen, but what can you do.</Source>
      <Dest>Smečky! To znamená, že celá nová část Nuka Worldu bude smrdět jak výběh brahmíny, ale co naděláme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00151E">
      <EDID>[010201CA]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>With the Galactic Zone under the Overboss' control, I mean... We're doing it, people! We're taking over Nuka-World!</Source>
      <Dest>A když superšéf ovládá Galaktickou zónu, chci říct... My to fakt dáme, lidi! Přebíráme kontrolu nad Nuka Worldem!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001523">
      <EDID>[010201D0]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>By the Overboss' decree, The Pack is now in charge out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Z rozhodnutí superšéfa to tam teď vede Smečka.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001525">
      <EDID>[010201CE]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>By the Overboss' decree, The Disciples are now in charge out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Z rozhodnutí superšéfa to tam teď vedou Stoupenci.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001526">
      <EDID>[010201C5]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>So if you're on their bad side, might want to think twice before heading in there to check it out.</Source>
      <Dest>Takže jestli s nima nemáte nejlepší vztahy, možná si to dobře rozmyslete, než se tam vydáte to omrknout.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00152C">
      <EDID>[010201C8]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You rejects understand what this means? Nuka-World is ours, man! The whole friggin' park!</Source>
      <Dest>Vy zmetci, chápete, co to znamená? Nuka World je náš, lidi! Celej podělanej park!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00152D">
      <EDID>[010201C2]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, anybody listening? Got some good news for you!</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, poslouchá někdo? Mám pro vás dobrý zprávy!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00152E">
      <EDID>[010201C3]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>All those damned robots in the Galactic Zone? No longer a problem, thanks to our kick-ass Overboss!</Source>
      <Dest>Všichni ti zatracený roboti v Galaktický zóně? Už nejsou problém, díky našemu drsnýmu superšéfovi!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001533">
      <EDID>[010201D3]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Operators! Maybe with something to do, they won't look so damned bored all the time.</Source>
      <Dest>Provozáků! Možná nebudou pořád vypadat tak hrozně znuděný, když teď budou mít, co dělat.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001536">
      <EDID>[010201D2]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Disciples! Let's hope they don't screw the place up in their own unique, creepy way.</Source>
      <Dest>Stoupenců! Jen doufejme, že to tam nepodělaj tím svým unikátním a děsivým způsobem.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001537">
      <EDID>[010201CC]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>And if it's ours, do you all realize what this means? Nuka-World... It all belongs to us! All of it! Hell yeah, man!</Source>
      <Dest>A jestli je naše, uvědomujete si, co to znamená? Nuka World... celej patří nám. Celej! Mazec, lidi!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001568">
      <EDID>[010201CF]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>By the Overboss' decree, The Operators are now in charge out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Z rozhodnutí superšéfa to tam teď vedou Provozáci.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015A4">
      <EDID>[010213CD]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015BB">
      <EDID>[010213C1]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I don't know what the Overboss has planned next, but man... Get behind him or get the hell out of his way.</Source>
      <Dest>Nevím, co superšéf plánuje na příště, ale lidi... Postavte se za ní nebo jí sakra uhněte z cesty.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015C2">
      <EDID>[010213C7]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Not only did someone survive the Gauntlet, but he took on Colter and won!</Source>
      <Dest>Nejen že někdo přežil Uličku smrti, ale postavil se Colterovi a vyhrál!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015CF">
      <EDID>[010213BE]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Well, whatever. I can't wait to see what our new leader has planned. At least... can't be any worse than Colter, right? Right?</Source>
      <Dest>Ale co. Už se nemůžu dočkat, až uvidím, co pro nás nový vůdce naplánoval. Alespoň... nemůže bejt horší než Colter, ne? Co?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015DD">
      <EDID>[010213D1]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015E2">
      <EDID>[010213C5]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>"What'd he do?" you ask. Oh, nothing much. Just accomplished what we've all been waiting for - taking Nuka-World over. ALL OF IT.</Source>
      <Dest>Ptáte se „Co udělal?“. Nic moc. Jen dokázal to, na co všichni celou dobu čekáme - ovládnul Nuka World. CELEJ.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015EC">
      <EDID>[010213CC]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015F0">
      <EDID>[010213C3]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>If you had any questions, you can now rest assured that our Overboss is a BAD. ASS.</Source>
      <Dest>Pokud jste pochybovali, můžu vás ujistit, že náš superšéf je drsňák.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015F2">
      <EDID>[010213BD]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Word's getting around that the Overboss has been seen meeting up with the head honchos for each of the gangs.</Source>
      <Dest>Říká se, že superšéf má schůzky s hlavouny každého z gangů.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015F3">
      <EDID>[010213D0]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0015FA">
      <EDID>[010213BC]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, hey - got some news for you all.</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, hej - mám pro vás nějaký novinky.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001606">
      <EDID>[010213C9]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You just wait - this new Overboss is the real deal, man. Getting shit done!</Source>
      <Dest>Jen počkejte - tenhle novej superšéf to myslí vážně. Vážně maká!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001608">
      <EDID>[010213CE]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00160A">
      <EDID>[010213BB]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, it's your main man RedEye here, sending out some big congratulations to our brand new Overboss!</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, tady váš nejlepší přítel Spojivka, posílám velkou gratulaci našemu novýmu superšéfovi!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00160B">
      <EDID>[010213CB]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00160D">
      <EDID>[010213C8]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Not only did someone survive the Gauntlet, but she took on Colter and won!</Source>
      <Dest>Nejen že někdo přežil Uličku smrti, ale postavil se Colterovi a vyhrál!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00160F">
      <EDID>[010213BF]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I already hear people talkin' about some secret agreement between Gage and the gangs, saying whoever took down Colter would take his place. You believe that?</Source>
      <Dest>Slyším, jak si lidi povídaj o nějaký tajný dohodě mezi Gagem a gangy, kdo sundal Coltera zaujme jeho místo. Věříte tomu?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001611">
      <EDID>[010213CA]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>That's right - we're takin' the park! The whole damn thing! Don't you shake your head at me - I'm telling you, that's what's going down.</Source>
      <Dest>Správně - přebíráme park! Celý tohle místo! Nekejvejte hlavama - říkám vám, přesně o tohle tady jde.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001614">
      <EDID>[010213C6]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>"What'd she do?" you ask. Oh, nothing much. Just accomplished what we've all been waiting for - taking Nuka-World over. ALL OF IT.</Source>
      <Dest>Ptáte se „Co udělala?“. Nic moc. Jen dokázala to, na co všichni celou dobu čekáme - ovládnula Nuka World. CELEJ.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001615">
      <EDID>[010213C0]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I don't know what the Overboss has planned next, but man... Get behind him or get the hell out of his way.</Source>
      <Dest>Nevím, co superšéf plánuje na příště, ale lidi... Postavte se za něj nebo mu sakra uhněte z cesty.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001619">
      <EDID>[010213C2]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>That's right - if you haven't heard, Colter is toast! He's worm-food!</Source>
      <Dest>Přesně tak - jestli jste to neslyšeli, Colter je minulost! Je potrava pro červy!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00161E">
      <EDID>[010213CF]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001627">
      <EDID>[010213BA]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>No one's told me shit yet, but doesn't take a genius to figure out what's going on...</Source>
      <Dest>Nikdo mi neřekl ani prd, ale nemusím bejt génius, abych si dal dva a dva dohromady...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00162B">
      <EDID>[010213C4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Ladies and gentlemen... There can be no more doubt!</Source>
      <Dest>Dámy a pánové... Nemůže být pochyb!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00170D">
      <EDID>[0102334D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Okay, you know what? Screw the Pack. Just... what a bunch of assholes.</Source>
      <Dest>Dobře, víte co? Do hajzlu se Smečkou. Já jen... je to banda pitomců.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001732">
      <EDID>[01022FF7]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Overboss has left The Operators in charge out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Superšéf to tam nechal na starosti Provozákům.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001734">
      <EDID>[0102334F]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You didn't get enough attention from mommy, so you're gonna throw a tantrum and take over the power station?</Source>
      <Dest>Nedostalo se vám dost pozornosti od maminky, tak dostanete záchvat vzteku a převezmete elektrárnu?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001738">
      <EDID>[01023341]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Well you know what? Screw. You. The Overboss is gonna grind you into the fuckin' dirt. In fact, I hope you're already bleeding out.</Source>
      <Dest>Tak víte co? Jděte. Do prdele. Superšéf vás rozdrtí na podělanej prach. Vlastně doufám, že už krvácíte.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00173A">
      <EDID>[01022FF1]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>All those crazy-ass mutated animals have been taken care of!</Source>
      <Dest>O všechny ty šílený zmutovaný zvířata bylo postaráno!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00173F">
      <EDID>[01022FF2]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Thanks to the hard work of our kick-ass Overboss, I am happy to report that the Safari zone is no longer a death trap!</Source>
      <Dest>Díky těžké dřině našeho drsnýho superšéfa, vám s radostí oznamuju, že Safari zóna už není smrtící past.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001743">
      <EDID>[01023003]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>At the Overboss' orders, the Disciples are now running the show out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Podle rozkazu superšéfa to tam teď vedou Stoupenci.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001744">
      <EDID>[01022FFF]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Our new Overboss has added a notch to his belt, and added the Plant to the list of places he's conquered for us.</Source>
      <Dest>Náš novej superšéf má další zářez, přidal stáčírnu na seznam míst, který pro nás obsadil.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001745">
      <EDID>[01023348]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Talk to your gang leaders about what YOU can do to help!</Source>
      <Dest>Zeptejte se svých vůdců gangu, jak VY můžete pomoct!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00174C">
      <EDID>[01023347]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Overboss is gonna make sure the whole damn Commonwealth knows who we are!</Source>
      <Dest>Superšéf zařídí, že celej blbej Commonwealth ví, kdo jsme!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00174D">
      <EDID>[01022FFB]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>If you've been keeping score at home, you know what this means... The whole god-damned park is ours! Yeah!</Source>
      <Dest>Jestli jste počítali skóre, tak víte, co to znamená... Celej zatracenej park je náš! Jo!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001750">
      <EDID>[01023001]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Our new Overboss has been good to his word, and taken over the Plant, meaning the whole friggin' park is ours. It's all ours, man!</Source>
      <Dest>Náš novej superšéf splnil svoje slovo. Obsadil stáčírnu, to znamená, že celej park je náš. Je to všechno naše, lidi!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001758">
      <EDID>[01023344]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Did I tell you, or what? I did! I told you! I said "This Overboss... shit's gonna get DONE" and look! Just look!</Source>
      <Dest>Říkal jsem vám to nebo ne? Říkal! Říkal jsem to! Řekl jsem „Tenhle superšéf... věci se sakra pohnou“ a podívejte se! Jen se podívejte!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00175B">
      <EDID>[01023346]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Now that Nuka-World is ours, we're branching out, taking over some of those shit-heap settlements in the Commonwealth, turning them into something better!</Source>
      <Dest>Když je teď Nuka World náš, rozdělíme se a obsadíme ty mizerný osady v Commonwealthu a uděláme z nich něco lepšího!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001761">
      <EDID>[01023342]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Oh yeah, you heard me! Gone are the days of sitting around on our asses while everything goes to shit...</Source>
      <Dest>Ou jé, slyšeli jste mě! Pryč jsou dny, kdy jsme jen seděli na zadku a všechno šlo do hajzlu...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001763">
      <EDID>[01023000]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Our new Overboss has added a notch to her belt, and added the Plant to the list of places she's conquered for us.</Source>
      <Dest>Náš novej superšéf má další zářez, přidala stáčírnu na seznam míst, který pro nás obsadila.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001777">
      <EDID>[0102333D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I mean... the Hell you think you're gonna accomplish? After everything the boss has done, you're gonna stand in his way?</Source>
      <Dest>Chci říct... čeho si kurva myslíte, že dosáhnete? Po tom všem, co superšéf dokázal, mu budete stát v cestě?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00178B">
      <EDID>[0102333F]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Do... Do you all even know how good we've got it right now? Boss is setting up a regular Empire out there!</Source>
      <Dest>Víte... Víte vy vůbec, jak je to teď pro nás skvělý? Šéf tu dává dohromady normální impérium!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001790">
      <EDID>[01023345]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Man, I tell you, just when I thought I couldn't love the Overboss any more...</Source>
      <Dest>Lidi, říkám vám, když už jsem si myslel, že nemůžu superšéfa milovat víc...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00179B">
      <EDID>[01023349]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>We are on top of the world, man. On TOP!</Source>
      <Dest>Jsme v sedmým nebi, lidi. V nebi!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017AA">
      <EDID>[01023336]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The rest of you out there - you know what I'm talking about. You see these assholes, you shoot 'em in the face.</Source>
      <Dest>A vy všichni ostatní - víte o čem mluvím. Jestli uvidíte ty kretény, pošlete jim kulku do hlavy.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017B6">
      <EDID>[01023340]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>So here's a little something for you... If you haven't heard, we're taking this show on the road!</Source>
      <Dest>Něco malýho tu pro vás mám... Jestli jste to ještě neslyšeli, tak se do toho pouštíme!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017B7">
      <EDID>[0102333C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Ladies and Gentlemen... Savages of all ages... We. Have. Done it!</Source>
      <Dest>Dámy a pánové... Barbaři každého věku... My. Jsme to. Zmákli!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017B9">
      <EDID>[01022FF9]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>This is it, everyone - we're taking over Nuka-World! I'm telling you, the Safari Zone is just the beginning!</Source>
      <Dest>A je to tady - obsadíme Nuka World! Říkám vám, Safari zóna je jen začátek!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017BE">
      <EDID>[01023002]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Our new Overboss has been good to her word, and taken over the Plant, meaning the whole friggin' park is ours. It's all ours, man!</Source>
      <Dest>Náš novej superšéf splnil svoje slovo. Obsadila stáčírnu, to znamená, že celej park je náš. Je to všechno naše, lidi!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017CB">
      <EDID>[01023005]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>At the Overboss' orders, The Pack is now running the show out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Podle rozkazu superšéfa to tam teď vede Smečka.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017D8">
      <EDID>[0102333E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I mean... the Hell you think you're gonna accomplish? After everything the boss has done, you're gonna stand in her way?</Source>
      <Dest>Chci říct... čeho si kurva myslíte, že dosáhnete? Po tom všem, co superšéf dokázal, jí budete stát v cestě?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017E3">
      <EDID>[01022FF4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You know how the bottling plant has been chock-full of Nukalurks for as long as we've been here?</Source>
      <Dest>Víte, jak je stáčírna přecpaná nukaplíživci celou tu dobu, co tu jsem?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0017F2">
      <EDID>[01022FFD]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Our new Overboss has proved he deserves the title, and cleared out the plant. It's finally safe for us!</Source>
      <Dest>Náš novej superšéf si ten titul zaslouží, dokázal to vyčištěním stáčírny. Konečně je tam pro nás bezpečno!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001800">
      <EDID>[0102334C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Okay, you know what? Screw the Operators. Just... what a bunch of assholes.</Source>
      <Dest>Dobře, víte co? Do hajzlu s Provozákama. Já jen... je to banda pitomců.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001801">
      <EDID>[01023004]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>At the Overboss' orders, The Operators are now running the show out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Podle rozkazu superšéfa to tam teď vedou Provozáci.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001802">
      <EDID>[01022FF8]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Overboss has left The Pack in charge out there - they're probably thrilled to have their own cages now.</Source>
      <Dest>Superšéf to tam nechal na starosti Smečce - jsou pravděpodobně unešený, že maj konečně svoje klece.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00180C">
      <EDID>[01022FFE]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Our new Overboss has proved she deserves the title, and cleared out the plant. It's finally safe for us!</Source>
      <Dest>Náš novej superšéf si ten titul zaslouží, dokázala to vyčištěním stáčírny. Konečně je tam pro nás bezpečno!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001812">
      <EDID>[0102334E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You didn't get enough attention from daddy, so you're gonna throw a tantrum and take over the power station?</Source>
      <Dest>Nedostalo se vám dost pozornosti od tatínka, tak dostanete záchvat vzteku a převezmete elektrárnu?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001815">
      <EDID>[01023338]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Your hero and mine, the Overboss, has made our dreams a reality!</Source>
      <Dest>Váš a můj hrdina superšéf udělal z našich snů realitu!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00181D">
      <EDID>[01023335]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>We're all out here, sweating and bleeding for the Boss' vision, and what - it's not enough for you?</Source>
      <Dest>Všichni se tady potíme a krvácíme pro superšéfovu představu a vy co - pro vás to není dost?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00181F">
      <EDID>[01022FF6]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Overboss has left the Disciples in charge out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Superšéf to tam nechal na starosti Stoupencům.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001820">
      <EDID>[01022FF3]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>If you're on good terms with 'em, maybe they'll share some caps with you. If you're not on good terms, well... Your loss, man.</Source>
      <Dest>Jestli jste s nima za dobře, možná se s váma podělí o pár zátek. Jestli nejste, no... pak je to vaše chyba.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001822">
      <EDID>[0102333B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You know what I'm talking about. You've seen the lights. It's... It's beautiful, isn't it?</Source>
      <Dest>Víte o čem mluvím. Viděli jste ty světla. Je to... Je to nádhera, že jo?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001829">
      <EDID>[0102334B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Okay, you know what? Screw the Disciples. Just... what a bunch of assholes.</Source>
      <Dest>Dobře, víte co? Do hajzlu se Stoupencema. Já jen... je to banda pitomců.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001831">
      <EDID>[01022FFA]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Overboss is on a roll now, right? Another zone is all ours!</Source>
      <Dest>Supešéfovi se teda daří, co? Další zóna je naše!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001832">
      <EDID>[01023337]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is now officially the best place in the world, and everyone everywhere knows it!</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka World je teď oficiálně nejlepší místo na světě a všichni všude to vědí!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001833">
      <EDID>[0102334A]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>If you haven't gotten in on this action yet, there's still time - the boss ain't done yet!</Source>
      <Dest>Jestli jste se do toho ještě nedali, pořád máte čas - superšéf ještě neskončil!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001834">
      <EDID>[01023334]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>And then you get right back up, get out there, and tear some shit up!</Source>
      <Dest>A pak zase vstaňte, vyjděte ven a způsobte někde pořádnej chaos!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00183C">
      <EDID>[01022FFC]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Like, I personally know at least three jackasses who got themselves killed trying to loot the place. Anyway, that ain't a problem no more!</Source>
      <Dest>Znám osobně nejmíň tři pitomce, co se nechali zabít, když se to tam snažili vykrást. Každopádně teď už to není problém!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001842">
      <EDID>[01023343]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Those Commonwealth pukes have rolled over and now work for us, or they're six feet under.</Source>
      <Dest>Ty blbouni v commonwelthu se dali na naši stranu a dělaj pro nás nebo se ocitnou pod kytičkama.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001843">
      <EDID>[01023339]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You see the Overboss, you get down on your friggin' knees and thank him. Without him, we'd be screwed.</Source>
      <Dest>Až uvidíte superšéfa, padněte na kolena a děkujte mu. Bez něj bysme byli v hajzlu.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001846">
      <EDID>[01022FF5]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, hey - got an update for you louses out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, hej - mám pro vás informace, vy krysy.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001854">
      <EDID>[0102333A]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You see the Overboss, you get down on your friggin' knees and thank her. Without her, we'd be screwed.</Source>
      <Dest>Až uvidíte superšéfa, padněte na kolena a děkujte jí. Bez ní bysme byli v hajzlu.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0018FE">
      <EDID>[01025B37]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I ever tell you all about the time I got my name?</Source>
      <Dest>Řekl jsem vám někdy o tom, kdy jsem dostal svoje jméno?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001902">
      <EDID>[01025B3E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>She took special care to put down the ghoul responsible for all that shit. The woman is thorough!</Source>
      <Dest>Osobně se ujistila, že zabila ghúla, kterej byl za to všechno zodpovědnej. Ta ženská je důkladná!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00190F">
      <EDID>[01025393]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001910">
      <EDID>[01025392]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001915">
      <EDID>[01025B39]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I say "Kiddie Kingdom" and you immediately think what? "Ghouls", right? Well, think again, halfwits!</Source>
      <Dest>Když řeknu „Dětské království“, co se vám hned vybaví? „Ghúlové“, že jo? No, tak přemejšlejte znova, idioti!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00191B">
      <EDID>[0102539D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You're all a bunch of psychopaths, and I love you for it. This is Raider Radio, and it's for you.</Source>
      <Dest>Jste všichni banda psychopatů a já vás za to miluju. Tohle je rádio nájezdníků a je tu jen pro vás.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00191C">
      <EDID>[01025394]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001922">
      <EDID>[01025B31]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Here's a little somethin' which I know you've all heard pieces of before. Only this time, you've got Redeye, the master of story-telling, to lay it on you.</Source>
      <Dest>Tady je něco, co jste z části určitě už všichni slyšeli. Jenže teď tu máte Spojivku, mistra ve vyprávění příběhů, kterej to na vás vysype.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001931">
      <EDID>[01025B3D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>He took special care to put down the ghoul responsible for all that shit. The man is thorough!</Source>
      <Dest>Osobně se ujistil, že zabil ghúla, kterej byl za to všechno zodpovědnej. Ten chlap je důkladnej!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001939">
      <EDID>[01025B2D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You all ever feel like you just can't get enough? Redeye hears you, man. He knows what it's like.</Source>
      <Dest>Cejtíte někdy, že nemáte dost? Spojivka vás slyší, lidi. On ví, jaký to je.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00193F">
      <EDID>[01025B3F]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Not only did the Overboss wade in there and wipe 'em out...</Source>
      <Dest>Nejen, že tam superšéf vtrhnul a vyhladil je...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001943">
      <EDID>[01025B3B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>He was nice enough to take the one ghoul left with half a brain, and give him a friggin' job. You believe that?</Source>
      <Dest>Byl tak hodnej, že jednomu ghúlovi, kterýmu zbylo půl mozku, dal práci. Věřili byste tomu?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001945">
      <EDID>[01025B2F]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>This one ain't about me. It's about this friend... that I have... who is not me.</Source>
      <Dest>Tahle není o mně. Je o příteli... kterého mám... a není já.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00194E">
      <EDID>[0102539C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>It's Redeye here, running Raider Radio. You love it, and you know it!</Source>
      <Dest>Tady Spojivka na rádiu nájezdníků. Když ho miluješ, není co řešit!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00194F">
      <EDID>[01025395]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001950">
      <EDID>[01025B3A]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Who wants some good news? You? Is it you? Because I got some!</Source>
      <Dest>Kdo chce nějaký dobrý zprávy? Ty? Chceš je ty? Protože já nějaký mám!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001956">
      <EDID>[0102539B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, asshole! You're listening to Raider Radio.</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, blbečku! Posloucháš rádio nájezdníků.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00195B">
      <EDID>[01025396]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00195C">
      <EDID>[01025B3C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>She was nice enough to take the one ghoul left with half a brain, and give him a friggin' job. You believe that?</Source>
      <Dest>Byla tak hodná, že jednomu ghúlovi, kterýmu zbylo půl mozku, dala práci. Věřili byste tomu?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00195F">
      <EDID>[01025B35]</EDID>
      <REC id="0">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>So, I was thinking about the time I came to Nuka-World. I ever tell you deadbeats that story?</Source>
      <Dest>Ta jsem přemejšlel o době, kdy jsem přišel do Nuka Worldu. Říkal jsem vám flákačům někdy tu historku?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="001960">
      <EDID>[0102539E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B0A">
      <EDID>[0103775E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention space pilots! Earth is under attack and you could be our only hope for survival! Ships are now boarding at Nuka-Galaxy.</Source>
      <Dest>Pozor vesmírní piloti! Země je pod útokem a vy můžete být naší jedinou nadějí na přežití! Nastupte do lodí v Nuka-Galaxy.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B0D">
      <EDID>[01037828]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>While touring Nuka-World, why not try a refreshing Nuka-Grape, Nuka-Orange or Nuka-Cherry. Now available at any one of our park concession stands.</Source>
      <Dest>Proč při procházce Nuka Worldem nezkusit osvěžující Nuka-Hrozno, Nuka-Pomeranč nebo Nuka-Cherry. Nyní dostupné v každém našem stánku.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B10">
      <EDID>[01037775]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention. We're happy to announce that Mad Mulligan's Mine Cart Ride has finally re-opened with stronger restraints following last year's tragedy.</Source>
      <Dest>Pozor. Rádi vám oznamujeme, že důlní dráha Šílenýho Mulligana je konečně opět otevřena, po loňské tragédii jsme posílili bezpečností opatření.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B13">
      <EDID>[010477DD]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention. In the event of an emergency, remain calm and obey all safety and shelter instructions provided by Nuka-World employees. Thank You.</Source>
      <Dest>Pozor. V případě nouzové situace zůstaňte klidní a řiďte se bezpečnostními pokyny zaměstnanců Nuka Worldu. Děkujeme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B14">
      <EDID>[0103777E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention guests. The last outbound tram to the Nuka-World Transit Center will be leaving the park promptly at 11:55 p.m. Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>Návštěvníci pozor. Poslední odjíždějící tramvaj do přepravní stanice Nuka Worldu bude z parku odjíždět přesně v 23:55. Děkujeme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B19">
      <EDID>[01037776]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Parents, don't forget to pick up your child's Nuka-Sheriff Star after today's Wild West Stunt Show performance. Yee-hah.</Source>
      <Dest>Rodiče, nezapomeňte si po kaskadérském představení Divoký západ vyzvednout odznaky šerifa pro vaše děti. Yee-hah.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B1A">
      <EDID>[01037769]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>We're happy to announce that the first ten guests to arrive at the Barry the Bear Show will receive a plush Barry to take home.</Source>
      <Dest>S radostí oznamujeme, že prvních deset návštěvníku představení medvěda Barryho dostane plyšového Barryho jako dárek.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B22">
      <EDID>[0103776A]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention, guests. To prevent limb-loss, please refrain from leaning over the railings at the Gator Wrestling Show. Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>Návštěvníci pozor. Abyste zabránili ztrátě končetin, prosíme nenaklánějte se přes zábradlí na zápasu s aligátory. Děkujeme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B32">
      <EDID>[01037773]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention, please. Today's performance of "Cappy-o and Bottle-ette" will begin in approximately fifteen minutes.</Source>
      <Dest>Prosím pozor. Dnešní představení „Zátky a Láhve“ začne přibližně za patnáct minut.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B3B">
      <EDID>[01037767]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>While touring the Gorilla House, please refrain from making rude gestures to any of our primate specimens. Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>Při prohlídce pavilonu goril se prosíme zdržte dělání neslušných gest na naše primáty. Děkujeme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B46">
      <EDID>[01037760]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Due to high demand, we've added a second performance of Queen Quantum's Quoronation. Please check your park brochure for details.</Source>
      <Dest>Kvůli vysoké poptávce jsme přidali druhé představení korunovace královny Quantum. Pro více informací se prosím podívejte do letáčku.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B4E">
      <EDID>[01037774]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Thirsty? Head over to Doc Phosphate's Saloon in Dry Rock Gulch to purchase an ice-cold Nuka-Cola Wild.</Source>
      <Dest>Máte žízeň? Zamiřte do Salónu doktora Fosfáta ve Vyprahlé rokli a kupte si ledově vychlazenou Nuka-Colu Wild.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B57">
      <EDID>[010477DF]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Parents, if you're looking for a refreshing way to make it through the day, try a Nuka-Cola Dark. Same great cola taste, with an alcohol twist.</Source>
      <Dest>Rodiče, pokud hledáte osvěžující způsob, jak přežít den, zkuste Nuka-Colu Dark. Stejná skvělá chuť koly říznutá alkoholem.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B59">
      <EDID>[0103776E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Don't forget to stake out a good spot for the Fizztop Mountain Fireworks Spectacular this evening. Show starts promptly at 9 p.m.</Source>
      <Dest>Nezapomeňte si na tento večer vyhlídnout dobrá místa pro úchvatný ohňostroj hory Šumák. Představení začíná  přesně v devět večer.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B5C">
      <EDID>[0103775C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Prepare to experience life beyond earth at "Among the Stars." Exhibit sponsored by a grant from the Vault-Tec Corporation.</Source>
      <Dest>Připravte se zažít život mimo Zemi v „Mezi hvězdami“. Výstava sponzorována společností Vault-Tec.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B67">
      <EDID>[01037779]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Tokens for the Midway Games are available at any one of the marked token dispensers in Dry Rock Gulch.</Source>
      <Dest>Žetony pro hry jsou dostupné v kterémkoliv označeném zásobníku žetonů ve Vyprahlé rokli.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B68">
      <EDID>[0103777C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is proud to be hosting our Quantum Celebration. Stop by Cappy's Cafe to sample Nuka-Cola's newest and most delicious flavor.</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka World je hrdým hostitelem festivalu Quantum. Zastavte se v Zátkově kavárně a ochutnejte nejnovější a nejlahodnější příchuť Nuka-Coly.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B71">
      <EDID>[010477DC]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is pleased to announce that a small portion of your admission fee will be donated to support our men and women fighting overseas.</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka-World s potěšením oznamuje, že malá část vašeho vstupného bude věnována na podporu našich mužů a žen bojujících v zámoří.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B7A">
      <EDID>[010477DB]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World's Great Halloween Spooktacular will begin next week. Reserve your tickets for this nighttime event at the main box office.</Source>
      <Dest>Velký Hrůzostrašný Haloween Nuka Worldu začíná příští týden. Rezervujte si lístky na na tuto noční událost v hlavní pokladně.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B7E">
      <EDID>[010477E0]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is proud to be the only East Coast location serving Nuka-Cola Quartz and Nuka-Cola Victory. Try one today!</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka World je hrdý, že jako jediný na východním pobřeží nabízí Nuka-Colu Quartz a Nuka-Colu Vítězství. Zkuste je ještě dnes!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B80">
      <EDID>[010477D9]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is proud to announce the grand re-opening of our World of Refreshment ride now featuring delicious Nuka-Cola Quantum.</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka World vám s potěšením oznamuje, že jsme znovuotevřeli naší atrakci Svět osvěžení, kam jsme přidali výtečnou Nuka-Colu Quantum.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B88">
      <EDID>[01037763]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Just a reminder that Nuka-World is not responsible for injuries sustained by the audience during the Cola Clowns Comedy Cavalcade.</Source>
      <Dest>Jen připomínáme, že Nuka World nenese zodpovědnost na zranění diváků utrpěná během komediální kavalkády Cola klaunů.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B93">
      <EDID>[01037766]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention. All contestants for the Nuka-Cola Drinking Contest must turn in their indemnity waviers before they will be allowed to participate.</Source>
      <Dest>Pozor. Všichni soutěžící Nuka Cola pijáckého klání musejí nejdříve odevzdat prohlášení o odpovědnosti, jinak jim nebude dovoleno se zúčastnit.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B9C">
      <EDID>[01037778]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Sickness bags are available for our more sensitive customers at the entrance to the Stampede Carousel.</Source>
      <Dest>Sáčky pro případ nevolnosti jsou pro naše citlivější zákazníky připraveny u vchodu ke Splašenému kolotoči.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002B9E">
      <EDID>[01037770]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention. All matinee showings of "The Phantom of the Nuka" at The Parlor are sold out. Tickets for evening showings are still available.</Source>
      <Dest>Pozor. Lístky na všechna odpolední představení „Fantom Nuky“ v Salónku jsou vyprodaná. Lístky pro večerní představení jsou pořád dostupná.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BA1">
      <EDID>[0103776B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Guide maps for our Hedge Maze are available for confused visitors at the Safari Adventure Park Office for only thirty-five dollars.</Source>
      <Dest>Pro zmatené návštěvníky jsou v kanceláři parku Safari dobrodružství připraveny za pouhých třicet pět dolarů mapy našeho bludiště.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BA3">
      <EDID>[010477DE]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Guests, if you're missing an item, stop by our Lost and Found at the Main Gate. Your item will be returned to you for a nominal fee.</Source>
      <Dest>Návštěvníci, pokud jste něco ztratili, zastavte se ve ztrátách a nálezech u hlavní brány. Vše vám za symbolický poplatek vrátíme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BA6">
      <EDID>[0103777A]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Mad Mullligan, Miss Trixie, Sheriff Bruce, One-Eyed Ike and Doc Phosphate are making their rounds at Dry Rock Gulch. Stop by for a photo opportunity.</Source>
      <Dest>Šílenej Mullligan, slečna Trixie, šerif Bruce, Jednookej Ike a doktor Fosfát obcházejí Vyprahlou Rokli. Zastavte se a udělejte si fotku.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BA8">
      <EDID>[0103775D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Tours for Star Control are now full for the day. Please speak to a park concierge for additional information.</Source>
      <Dest>Prohlídky řízení STAR jsou pro dnešek už plné. Pro více informací se prosím zeptejte správce parku.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BAC">
      <EDID>[01037771]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Guests, remember to redeem all your prize tickets at the Nuka-Cade before you head home. Located in Nuka-Town U.S.A.</Source>
      <Dest>Návštěvníci, nezapomeňte si v Nukamatu vyměnit svoje výherní lístky než vyrazíte domů. Najdete ho v Nuka Townu.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BB7">
      <EDID>[0103776D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Due to a mix-up at Safari Adventure's Animal Waste Facility, apple juice will not be served this evening at the Four Leaf Fried Fish Restaurant.</Source>
      <Dest>Kvůli chybě v zařízení pro zpracování odpadu v Safari dobrodružství, nebude dnes nabízen jablečný džus v restauraci smažených ryb Čtyřlístek.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BBB">
      <EDID>[0103775F]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Come witness the majesty and the pageantry of King Cola's Court. Tickets for all showings available now at the Kiddie Kingdom Box Office.</Source>
      <Dest>Přijďte a buďte svědky velkoleposti a nádhery Dvora krále Coly. Lístky na všechna představení jsou k dispozici na pokladně Dětského království.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BBE">
      <EDID>[0103775A]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Just a reminder for our guests that tonight's bout at the RobCo Battlezone is almost sold out. Purchase your tickets now.</Source>
      <Dest>Připomínáme našim návštěvníkům, že lístky na dnešní bitvu v Bojové zóně RobCo jsou téměř vyprodané. Neváhejte s koupí lístků.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BC0">
      <EDID>[01037777]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Shoes ruined at the Barnyard Animal Petting Zoo? Pick up a new pair at the Dry Rock Gulch gift shop for only fifty dollars.</Source>
      <Dest>Máte zničené boty z dětské zoo U Stodoly? Nový pár si v dárkovém obchodě ve Vyprahlé rokli můžete vybrat jen za padesát dolarů.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BC2">
      <EDID>[0103775B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Tonight's showing at the Starlight Interstellar Theater will be "Night of the Fish Man's Revenge." Not recommended for children under 5.</Source>
      <Dest>Dnešní představení v kině Mezihvězdný třpyt bude „Noc pomsty rybího muže“. Nedoporučujeme pro děti mladší pěti let.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BC6">
      <EDID>[01037761]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention please, the one p.m. and three p.m. performances for Oswald the Outrageous are sold out. Limited tickets for 5 p.m. are still available.</Source>
      <Dest>Prosím pozor, lístky pro představení Fantastického Osvalda v jednu a ve tři jsou vyprodané. Volné je omezené množství lístků pro představení v pět.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BD7">
      <EDID>[0103776F]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Remember to show your park admission stub to get half off an order of Nuka-Fries at Cappy's Cafe in Nuka-Town U.S.A.</Source>
      <Dest>Nezapomeňte ukázat svůj ústřižek vstupenky, abyste získali poloviční slevu na objednávku Nuka Hranolek v Zátkově kavárně v Nuka Townu.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BDA">
      <EDID>[010477DA]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Reserve your tickets now and be the first to ride our Angry Anaconda Coaster opening soon at Safari Adventure.</Source>
      <Dest>Rezervujte si lístky a buďte první, kdo se projede na dráze Rozzlobená anakonda, kterou brzy otevřeme v Safari dobrodružství.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BDD">
      <EDID>[01037772]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention guests. If you've lost your Hidden Cappy Glasses, additional pairs can be purchased from any souvenir stand in any of our parks.</Source>
      <Dest>Návštěvníci pozor. Pokud jste ztratili brýle pro Najdi Zátku, další si můžete koupit v každém stánku se suvenýry v kterémkoliv parku.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BDF">
      <EDID>[01037764]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention parents, we still have fourteen unclaimed children recovered from the Fun House. You can pick them up at the entrance to Kiddie Kingdom.</Source>
      <Dest>Upozornění pro rodiče, stále máme čtrnáct nevyzvednutých dětí nalezených v Domě zábavy. Můžete si je vyzvednout u vstupu do Dětského království.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BE1">
      <EDID>[01037762]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Due to unforeseen circumstances, the daily duel of Nuka-Knight and the Nuka-Cola Dark Knight has been postponed until further notice.</Source>
      <Dest>Kvůli neočekávaným okolnostem byl denní souboj mezi Nuka-rytířem a Nuka-temným rytířem do odvolání odložen.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002BE3">
      <EDID>[01037768]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention guests. In case of emergency, anti-venom is available at the exit for the Reptile House.</Source>
      <Dest>Návštěvníci pozor. V případě nouze je protijed k dispozici u východu pavilonu plazů.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002FB6">
      <EDID>[0103B91B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, this is your man Redeye, running Raider Radio. Don't like the name? I don't give a shit!</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, tady je váš Spojivka na rádiu nájezdníků. Nelíbí se vám moje jméno? Je mi to úplně volný!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002FC0">
      <EDID>[0103B913]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I didn't vote for this broad! How come she gets to be Overboss?</Source>
      <Dest>Pro tuhle ženskou jsem nehlasoval! Jak to, že bude superšéf?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002FC2">
      <EDID>[0103B90E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I mean, Hell... If I'd known they were looking for somebody, I'd have thrown my name in that hat, you know what I'm saying?</Source>
      <Dest>Ksakru... Kdybych věděl, že někoho hledáme, sám bych se nabídnul. Víte, jak to myslím?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="002FF0">
      <EDID>[0103B912]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I didn't vote for this guy! How come he gets to be Overboss?</Source>
      <Dest>Pro tohohle chlápka jsem nehlasoval! Jak to, že bude superšéf?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0030F1">
      <EDID>[0103E429]</EDID>
      <REC id="1">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You go to any of the other parks, and odds are you ain't coming back. Don't say I didn't warn ya.</Source>
      <Dest>Jestli půjdete do nějakého jiného parku, je velká šance, že se už nevrátíte. Neříkejte, že jsem vás nevaroval.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0030FC">
      <EDID>[0103E427]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, little announcement for you idiots out there:</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, malý oznámení pro vás idioty:</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003104">
      <EDID>[0103E43D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>You remember when Colter said we'd take over all of Nuka-World, and then he didn't do shit to make it happen?</Source>
      <Dest>Pamatujete si, jak Colter řekl, že převezmeme Nuka World a pak nehnul ani prstem, aby se tak stalo?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00311E">
      <EDID>[0103E42D]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Well - in case you ain't heard, things have gone from "bad" to "totally screwed"!</Source>
      <Dest>V případě, že jste to neslyšeli, situace se změnila z „špatná“ na „úplně v hajzlu“!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003151">
      <EDID>[0103E42B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Me? I'm getting the hell out of here! Consider this your official notice that "Raider Radio" is off the damn air - FOREVER!</Source>
      <Dest>Já? Já odsud sakra mizím! Považujte to za oficiální prohlášení, že „rádio nájezdníků“ končí s vysíláním - NAVŽDY!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003167">
      <EDID>[0103E42A]</EDID>
      <REC id="1">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Unless you wanna wind up dead, keep your asses out of parks we ain't secured. There's all kinds of weird shit out there.</Source>
      <Dest>Pokud nechcete skončit mrtvý, držte svý prdele dál od parků, který nejsou zabezpečený. Je tam spousta divnejch věcí.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003168">
      <EDID>[0103E42A]</EDID>
      <REC id="0">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>We got a new Overboss and all, but we're still stuck with the mess Colter left us in.</Source>
      <Dest>Máme novýho superšéfa a tak, ale pořád se musíme vypořádat s tím průserem, v kterým nás tu Colter nechal.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003177">
      <EDID>[0103E43B]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003182">
      <EDID>[0103E428]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Look how far we've come. Pretty great, isn't it?!</Source>
      <Dest>Podívejte se, jak daleko jsme se dostali. Docela dobrý, ne?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003206">
      <EDID>[0103E430]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003210">
      <EDID>[0103E42C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Our new Overboss turned on us, and has been wiping out Raiders left and right!</Source>
      <Dest>Náš novej superšéf se obrátil proti nám a střílí nájezdníky nalevo i napravo!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003216">
      <EDID>[0103E42F]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The rest of you wanna try and fight her, go right on ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>Ostatní, co se jí chcete postavit a bojovat, jen do toho.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00321C">
      <EDID>[0103E43C]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00322C">
      <EDID>[0103E43A]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00322E">
      <EDID>[0103E429]</EDID>
      <REC id="0">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I know you think you're really tough, and that nothing scares you, but do yourself a favor and stick to Nuka-Town.</Source>
      <Dest>Myslíte si, jak jste drsný a nic vás nevyděsí, ale udělejte si laskavost a držte se v Nuka Townu.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003230">
      <EDID>[0103E438]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey... Hey, guys. I've got a fun one for you...</Source>
      <Dest>Hele... Hele, lidi. Mám pro vás něco zajimavýho...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003235">
      <EDID>[0103E42E]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The rest of you wanna try and fight him, go right on ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>Ostatní, co se mu chcete postavit a bojovat, jen do toho.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0033BD">
      <EDID>[01040CEC]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Uhh, Nisha has the following to say to the Pack: "Take one more shit on our lawn, and we'll put you down." Hoo boy! I don't write 'em, folks - I just read 'em.</Source>
      <Dest>Uhh, Nisha by ráda Smečce řekla následující: „Jestli se nám ještě jednou vyděláte na trávník, tak vás pod něj zahrabem.“ No ty vole! Já to nepíšu, lidi, já to jen čtu.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0033C3">
      <EDID>[01040CEE]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I hear Dixie is looking for volunteers for target practice. I quote: "Fun will be had by all." I, uhh... I'd think twice before raising my hand for that one.</Source>
      <Dest>Slyšel jsme, že Dixie hledá dobrovolníky na střelbu na terče. Cituju: „Pro všechny to bude zábava.“ Já, no... dobře bych si to promyslel, než bych se přihlásil.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0033EB">
      <EDID>[01040CE4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0033EF">
      <EDID>[010415CC]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>This here is Raider Radio - don't forget, if you've got something you want everyone to hear, you're probably wrong and whatever it is sucks. But if you insist, drop us a note and we'll read it on-air.</Source>
      <Dest>Tohle je rádio nájezdníků - nezapomeňte, jestli chcete něco říct světu, pak je to pravděpodobně úplná krávovina. Ale jestli na tom trváte, tak nám napište a my to odvysíláme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0033FD">
      <EDID>[01040CF5]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Got a note here: "The Pack rules!" Okay, sure, and on the back is... no. Damn it, Mason, I told you - I am NOT howling. Ever.</Source>
      <Dest>Mám tu vzkaz: „Smečka je boží!“ Tak jo, jasně a na zadní straně je... ne. Sakra Masone, říkal jsem ti - nebudu výt. Nikdy.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00341B">
      <EDID>[01040CEA]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, let's get personal for a second here, assholes. Whoever dropped a frag down my favorite toilet... If I find you, you are going to die. Slowly. And Painfully.</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, teď na chvíli něco trochu osobního, pitomci. Kdokoliv hodil granát do mýho oblíbenýho záchodu... Jestli tě najdu, tak umřeš. Pomalu. A bolestivě.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00341E">
      <EDID>[01040CF0]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Real quick: Whoever gutted an outside trader and piked him right in front of the gates - your handiwork was impressive, but not exactly good for business. Maybe keep that shit at home?</Source>
      <Dest>Jenom rychle: Kdo vykuchal obchodníka a napíchnul ho před hlavní bránu - tvoje práce byla působivá, ale není to dobrý pro naše podnikáni. Možná si to pro příště nech na doma?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003426">
      <EDID>[01040CE6]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00343B">
      <EDID>[01040CF2]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Anonymous note has come in: "Whoever's dumping bodies in the swan pond - thanks. Totally set the mood for a romantic evening, it really paid off." Damn, you all are disgusting.</Source>
      <Dest>Přišel anonymní vzkaz: „Kdokoliv hážete mrtvoly do labutího jezírka - dík. Vážně to naladí tu pravou atmosféru na romantickej večer, fakt se to vyplatilo.“ Sakra, vy jste tak nechutný.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00343C">
      <EDID>[010415D3]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>A general note: to all the assholes sending in notes saying you can do my job better than me, I'll see you all in hell.</Source>
      <Dest>Obecná poznámka: pro všechny blbce posílající mi vzkazy, že dokážou moji práci dělat líp než já, uvidíme se v pelke.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003453">
      <EDID>[01040CE5]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source> </Source>
      <Dest> </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00346A">
      <EDID>[01040CF7]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>And now, a note: "If someone left an ear in one of the teacups, I got it." There is no name, so... I guess if it's your ear, good luck getting it back.</Source>
      <Dest>A teď jeden vzkaz: „Jestli někdo nechal ucho v jednom z hrnků, tak ho mám.“ Není tu jméno, takže... jestli je to něčí ucho, tak hodně štěstí s jeho nalezením.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003479">
      <EDID>[01040CEB]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nisha has asked that I pass this along: "Mags - Steal from us again, and we'll redecorate Fizztop with Operator Blood." Yikes, sounds personal.</Source>
      <Dest>Nisha mě požádala, abych tohle přečetl: „Mags, ještě jednou nám něco ukradneš a vyzdobíme Šumák krví Provozáků.“ Jaj, to zní osobně.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00347E">
      <EDID>[01040CF3]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Yet another anonymous note: "Dear Overboss - if you're listening to this, you're dumber than I thought." What... What is that even supposed to mean?</Source>
      <Dest>Další anonymní vzkaz: „Drahý superšéfe, jestli tohle poslouchá, jsi blbější, než jsem si myslel.“ Co... Co to má vůbec znamenat?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003491">
      <EDID>[010415D4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Uhh, the Operators would like me to announce that they are hosting a free dinner, for all gang members interested in... nope, they're trying to posion you. Don't go to that.</Source>
      <Dest>No, Provozáci by rádi oznámili, že pořádají večeři zdarma pro všechny členy gangů, který maj zájem... houby, chtěj vás otrávit. Nelezte tam.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034AC">
      <EDID>[01040CF1]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Got a note here for NIRA, which is... uhh, now that I read this... is this a friggin' love letter? Are you shitting me? NIRA's a robot, you idiot.</Source>
      <Dest>Mám tu vzkaz pro NIRU, je to... uhh, když to tak čtu... to je zkurvenej milostnej dopis? Děláte si ze mě prdel? NIRA je robot, idioti.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034AF">
      <EDID>[01040CEF]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>A quick note: whoever stole my whiskey bottle - joke's on you! That ain't whiskey! You go right on ahead and keep it!</Source>
      <Dest>Rychlá poznámka: kdokoliv ukrad mojí flašku whisky - užij si ji! To není whisky! Takže si ji klidně nech.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034E0">
      <EDID>[01040CE8]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I have a note here, folks, about a missing person.... and I'm not going to bother reading it. C'mon, you all know by now that "missing" means "dead."</Source>
      <Dest>Mám tu vzkaz o pohřešovaný osobě... a nebudu se obtěžovat to číst. No tak, všichni víte, že „pohřešovaný“ znamená „mrtvý“.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034E1">
      <EDID>[01040CF4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>General announcement: I don't know where this rumor started that my name is Russell, but... well, it's Redeye, okay? Just Redeye. Forget this Russell shit.</Source>
      <Dest>Obecný oznámení: Nevím, kde se vzala fáma, že se jmenuju Russell, ale... no, jsem Spojivka, jasný? Jen Spojivka. Zapomeňte na tu kravinu s Russellem.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034E8">
      <EDID>[01040CF6]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I have a note here from Mags to Mason: "Flaming bags of shit? That the best you can do?" Okay, I'm sorry, but that's funny. Stupid as hell, but funny.</Source>
      <Dest>Mám tu vzkaz pro Masona od Mags: „Hořící pytel hoven? Nic lepšího neumíš?“ Dobře, promiňte, ale je to srandovní. Hloupý ale srandovní.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034F2">
      <EDID>[01040CE7]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, here's a friendly reminder: sure, nobody likes the traders. But you can't kill 'em all, or else there won't be anyone around to do all the shitty work you assholes won't do. Think about it.</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, přátelské upozornění: jasně, nikdo nemá rád obchodníky. Ale nemůžete je všechny zabít nebo nezbude nikdo, kdo by dělal všechnu tu podělanou práci, kterou vy dělat nechcete. Přemejšlejte o tom.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034FD">
      <EDID>[010415D5]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Got a note here, from.... guess it's someone in The Pack. It's a drawing... of William Black, and... that's a, uhh... okay, no. I'm tearing this up.</Source>
      <Dest>Mám tu vzkaz od... asi někoho ze Smečky. Je to obrázek... Williama Blacka a... je to, hmm.... dobře, ne. Trhám to na kusy.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0034FE">
      <EDID>[01040CED]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, any of you hear that Nisha once - supposedly - took out an entire raider gang by herself? Looking for facts and/or proof. Come talk to me.</Source>
      <Dest>Hej slyšel někdo z vás o tom, že Nisha údajně jednou zničila celej nájezdnickej gang sama? Sháním fakta nebo důkazy. Přijďte za mnou.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003506">
      <EDID>[01040CE9]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Here's an announcement from Mags Black: "To the Disciple who found a red ribbon on her bunk this morning - you know what you did. As do we." God, she even writes like a... Sorry, mic is still on.</Source>
      <Dest>Mám tu oznámení od Mags Blackové: „Stoupenci, který ráno našel červenou pásku na svojí posteli - víš, co jsi udělal. A my taky.“ Bože, ona i píše jako... Pardon, mikrofon je pořád zapnutej.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003624">
      <EDID>[0101F1F5]</EDID>
      <REC id="1">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>I mean... that's what my friend said. When he told me the story, and then I went and wrote a song about it. Whatever.</Source>
      <Dest>Chci říct... to mi řekl můj přítel. Když mi řekl svůj příběh a když jsem šel a napsal o tom písničku. To je fuk.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003864">
      <EDID>[010431A3]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Operators are now kings of the castle out there, so you lot play nice!</Source>
      <Dest>Provozáci jsou teď králové místního hradu, takže se chovejte slušně!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="0038BE">
      <EDID>[010431A4]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Pack are now kings of the castle out there, so you lot play nice!</Source>
      <Dest>Smečka je teď královská rodina místního hradu, takže se chovejte slušně!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003910">
      <EDID>[010431A2]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>The Disciples are now Kings... I guess Queens?... of the castle out there, so you lot play nice!</Source>
      <Dest>Stoupenci jsou teď králové... Nebo teda královny?... hradu, co tam je, takže se chovejte slušně!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003DE9">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements08</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is proud to announce the grand re-opening of our World of Refreshment ride now featuring delicious Nuka-Cola Quantum.</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka World vám s potěšením oznamuje, že jsme znovuotevřeli naší atrakci Svět osvěžení, kam jsme přidali výtečnou Nuka-Colu Quantum.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003DF8">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements05</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is pleased to announce that a small portion of your admission fee will be donated to support our men and women fighting overseas.</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka-World s potěšením oznamuje, že malá část vašeho vstupného bude věnována na podporu našich mužů a žen bojujících v zámoří.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003E1C">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements06</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World's Great Halloween Spooktacular will begin next week. Reserve your tickets for this nighttime event at the main box office.</Source>
      <Dest>Velký Hrůzostrašný Haloween Nuka Worldu začíná příští týden. Rezervujte si lístky na na tuto noční událost v hlavní pokladně.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003E1F">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements02</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Parents, if you're looking for a refreshing way to make it through the day, try a Nuka-Cola Dark. Same great cola taste, with an alcohol twist.</Source>
      <Dest>Rodiče, pokud hledáte osvěžující způsob, jak přežít den, zkuste Nuka-Colu Dark. Stejná skvělá chuť koly říznutá alkoholem.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003E21">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements04</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Attention. In the event of an emergency, remain calm and obey all safety and shelter instructions provided by Nuka-World employees. Thank You.</Source>
      <Dest>Pozor. V případě nouzové situace zůstaňte klidní a řiďte se bezpečnostními pokyny zaměstnanců Nuka Worldu. Děkujeme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003E22">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements03</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Guests, if you're missing an item, stop by our Lost and Found at the Main Gate. Your item will be returned to you for a nominal fee.</Source>
      <Dest>Návštěvníci, pokud jste něco ztratili, zastavte se ve ztrátách a nálezech u hlavní brány. Vše vám za symbolický poplatek vrátíme.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003E24">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements01</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Nuka-World is proud to be the only East Coast location serving Nuka-Cola Quartz and Nuka-Cola Victory. Try one today!</Source>
      <Dest>Nuka World je hrdý, že jako jediný na východním pobřeží nabízí Nuka-Colu Quartz a Nuka-Colu Vítězství. Zkuste je ještě dnes!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003E47">
      <EDID>DLC04RadioAnnouncements07</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Reserve your tickets now and be the first to ride our Angry Anaconda Coaster opening soon at Safari Adventure.</Source>
      <Dest>Rezervujte si lístky a buďte první, kdo se projede na dráze Rozzlobená anakonda, kterou brzy otevřeme v Safari dobrodružství.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003E72">
      <EDID>[01025B35]</EDID>
      <REC id="1">INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Doesn't matter - I feel like telling it now. Shut up.</Source>
      <Dest>To je jedno - chci vám ji teď říct. Držte zobáky.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003EC8">
      <EDID>[01049657]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Here's a note that came in: "Hey Redeye, I heard you were wondering where Super Mutants came from. Maybe you should ask your mom." Real classy, jackass.</Source>
      <Dest>Právě přišel vzkaz: „Hele Spojivko, prej by tě zajímalo, kde se vzali supermutanti. Možná se zeptej svojí mámi.“ Fakt na úrovni, debile.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003EEC">
      <EDID>[010487C6]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, whoever convinced NIRA to stand over me while I was sleeping, thanks a lot. You owe me a new mattress.</Source>
      <Dest>Hele, kdokoliv přesvědčil NIRU, aby nade mnou stála, když spím, fakt díky. Dlužíš mi novou matraci.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003F15">
      <EDID>[01049658]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, anybody else getting a little tired of drinking Nuka-Cola? I mean, it beats dying of thirst, I guess, but uhh, my teeth ain't looking so good.</Source>
      <Dest>Hele, někdo další má taky dost pití Nuka Coly? Chci říct, je to lepší než zemřít žízní, ale hmmm, moje zuby nevypadaj moc dobře.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="003F3A">
      <EDID>[01049659]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>To the Operators that sent in a tape of their own song they'd like me to play on the radio: not a friggin' chance. It killed my dog, man. Like, he literally dropped dead when he heard it.</Source>
      <Dest>Provozákům, kteří mi poslali pásku s vlastní písničkou a chtěj, ať ji pustím do rádia: bez šance. Zabila mi psa. Jako že opravdu padnul mrtvej, když to slyšel.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00415C">
      <EDID>[0104B1A7]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Just a thought: if any of you out there are thinking about crossing the Overboss, ask Nisha how that'll work out for you. Oh, that's right - you can't, cause she's friggin' dead. Chew on that.</Source>
      <Dest>Jen taková myšlenka: jestli někdo z vás přemejšlý, že podrazí superšéfa, zeptejte se Nishy, jak to s váma dopadne. Ou, to je pravda - nemůžete, protože je sakra mrtvá. Přemejšlejte o tom.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00415E">
      <EDID>[0104B1A9]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>If you ain't already noticed, seems like the Overboss is playin' favorites, with the Disciples at the top of the list. Good for them, I guess. Sucks to be anybody else.</Source>
      <Dest>Jestli jste si ještě nevšimli, vypadá to, že superšéf má na seznamu oblíbenců na prvním místě Stoupence. Pro ně to je asi dobře. Je na prd bejt někdo jinej.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="004210">
      <EDID>[0104B1A8]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Here's some friendly advice to anyone thinking about screwing over the Overboss: chat with Mason about how that'll go. Oh, that's right - you can't, cause the Overboss wiped out his whole friggin' gang.</Source>
      <Dest>Tady je přátelská rada každýmu, kdo by chtěl podrazit superšéfa: zeptejte se Masona, jak to šlo. Ou, vlastně to nejde, protože superšéf celej ten podělanej gang vyhladil.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="004238">
      <EDID>[0104B1AB]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Have you all noticed that the Pack are being handed a lot of territory lately? I guess the Overboss has taken a liking to 'em. Kinda surprising, since no one ever likes them.</Source>
      <Dest>Všimli jste si, jak Smečka dostává poslední dobou hodně území? Řekl bych, že je superšéf má rád. To je překvapující, když je nikdy nikdo nemá rád.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00423B">
      <EDID>[0104B1AA]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>If you ain't been payin attention, the Overboss is giving a lot of territory to the Operators. Good for them, sucks for everyone else.</Source>
      <Dest>Jestli jste nedávali pozor, tak superšéf dává hodně území Provozákům. Dobře pro ně, pro ostatní to je na prd.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" sID="00423E">
      <EDID>[0104B1A6]</EDID>
      <REC>INFO:NAM1</REC>
      <Source>Hey, if you're out there, thinking about crossing the Overboss, ask Mags how that'll work out for you. Oh, that's right - you can't, cause the Overboss killed her.</Source>
      <Dest>Hej, jestli přemejšlíte o tom, že podrazíte superšéfa, zeptejte se Mag, jak to s váma dopadne. Ou, to je pravda - nemůžete, protože ji superšéf zabil.</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
