following total atomic annihilation
the rebuilding of this great nation of
ours may fall to you that's why we at
Walt Tech have prepared these
educational materials for you to better
understand the seven defining attributes
that make you special now let's discuss
the uses of agility a nuclear blast and
the subsequent fallout will have many
adverse effects on life as we know it
intensive prolonged radiation exposure
may transform those above ground into
decrepit rotting beings that have lost
their ability to reason they will likely
be without common manners and quick to
anger you must learn to make the most of
available firearms but enthusiasm will
only take you so far now let's try that
again and remember that with your
impressive agility
you can act more decisively in glance
see it's a snap
agility can also help you out in
difficult moments
but why place yourself under undue
stress instead try a simpler route
taking the quieter approach is always
worth consideration your agility can
turn a sneak attack into a complete
tactical move keep in mind others may
have the same bright idea your agility
will help you move through the wasteland
with ease and yield other benefits like
assaulting an unsuspecting dreamer for
the king in hastily reloading your
firearms by piling on damage to
additional targets when the firm
regularly study your vault-tec provided
materials to prepare for survival and to
answer the question do you know what
makes you special