following total atomic annihilation the
rebuilding of this great nation of ours
may fall to you that's why we at Walt
Tech have prepared these educational
materials for you to better understand
the seven defining attributes that make
you special
and now charisma what is it made of
unlike the clean wholesome America you
may recall the wasteland will be a
distrustful place full of unsavory
characters and a few morals
earning the trust of your fellow man is
an often overlooked key to survival one
way to prove your trustworthiness is
through fair commercial exchange your
renowned charisma will enable more
favorable bartering don't get greedy now
use your charismatic nature to negotiate
your way out of tense moments having
friends is always of value how else do I
find friends you may wonder you may find
an impromptu cocktail hour helps to ease
social stress your charisma will help
you avoid the perils of addiction but
not the immediate effects of drink so
practice moderation or you'll find out
who your real friends are the hard way
you will find that even wild animals can
be charmed by your charisma looks like
you found a new pal bull don't get
carried away there big fella
oh so you see taking the charismatic
approach is more than just good manners
working with man's best friend into more
loyal companions will preventing others
to act on your behalf
regularly study your vault-tec provided
materials to prepare for survival
and to answer the question do you know
what makes you special