I can feel it wash over me the heat of
force the radiation of fear it's the end
of the world all over again I close my
eyes I see my life before all of this
before the bombs
everything can change in an instant and
the future you plan for yourself shifts
whether or not you're ready
at some point
it happens to all of us this wasn't the
world I wanted but
it was the one I found myself in the
cunt
my home
ripped apart and put back together
I thought I hoped I could find my family
cheap time make us whole again the way
we were but now I know I know I can't go
back and I know the world has changed
but the road ahead will be hard
this time I'm ready
because I know
never changes
I've lost Shawn all over
again I close my eyes I see my life
before all of this before the bombs
everything can change in an instant and
the future you plan for yourself shifts
whether or not you're ready at some
point
it happens to all of us
this wasn't the world I wanted but
it was the one I found myself in
the Commonwealth my home
ripped apart and put back together
I thought I hoped I could find my family
cheat time make us whole again
we were but now I know I know I can't go
back I know the world has changed and
that the road ahead will be hard this
time I'm ready
because I know war
never changes