I can feel it wash over me the heat the
force radiation the fear it's the end of
the world all over again I close my eyes
I see my life before all of this before
the bombs
everything can change in an instant and
the future you plan for yourself shifts
whether or not you're ready
at some point
it happens to all of us this was not the
world I wanted
but it was the one I found myself in the
common law
my home
ripped apart and put back together
I thought my I hoped I could find my
family
she'd time make us whole again the way
we were but now I know I know
I can't go back I know the world has
changed the road ahead will be hard
because I know or
war never changes
I've lost Sean all
over again I closed my eyes I see my
life before all of this before the bombs
everything can change in an instant in
the future you plan for yourself shifts
whether or not you're ready at some
point
it happens to all of us
this was not the world I wanted
but it was the one I found myself in
the common wolf my home
ripped apart and put back together
I thought by I hoped I could find my
family
sheep time make us whole again the way
we were but now I know I know I can't go
back I know the world has changed the
road ahead will be hard
this time I'm ready
because I know
or never changes