following total atomic annihilation the
rebuilding of this great nation of ours
may fall to you that's why we at
vault-tec have prepared these
educational materials for you to better
understand seven defining attributes
that make you special our topic today is
endurance we will all be faced with many
new and unfamiliar health risks such as
infection sudden loss of limb and above
all harmful radiation fortunately your
formidable endurance has turned your
body into a hard-working machine that
can resist the harmful effects of
radiation and physical violence like any
machine then your body must be
well-maintained to stay in tip-top shape
while average joes will survive on old
packaged standbys your ironclad insides
will allow you to seek fresh meat
radiation poisoning may have enlarged
your favorite meals
this means more healthful nutrition for
you take caution not to bite off more
than you can chew endurance can also
provide new options for food some of
which can be an acquired taste
gone are the days of exercising for fun
instead you will need to combine
athletics with crucial survival
activities the greater your endurance
the further you can go just be certain
to be mindful of others build your
endurance and soon you will find ways
that it improves your life above ground
added confidence in the swimming pool
stronger more resilient limbs to talk
the flesh of your fellow man can travel
regularly study your vault-tec provided
materials to prepare for survival and to
answer the question do you know what
makes you special