following total atomic annihilation the
rebuilding of this great nation of ours
may fall to you that's why we at
vault-tec have prepared these
educational materials for you to better
understand the seven defining attributes
that make you special
our next area of attention is
intelligence with all the talk of
physical survival in the wasteland you
may forget that sometimes it's survival
of the smartest an empty mind is a
vessel for knowledge and intelligence is
the key to unlocking opportunity and
adapting to your new world above ground
your advanced know-how will grant you
access to new places and new
technologies space age isn't it
intelligent survivors are also more
inventive creating technological wonders
of their own note that the s in science
stands for safety and when the tables
are turned against you don't be afraid
to set aside your refined intelligence
for the raw instincts of survival
just don't lose your head
advanced learning in the field of
intelligence can offer even more
benefits in this modern age of wonder to
start navigating with technological ease
keep blood where it belongs by helix in
creating more potent chemical compounds
from regularly study your vault-tec
provided materials to prepare for
survival and to answer the question do
you know what makes you special