following total atomic annihilation the
rebuilding of this great nation of ours
may fall to you that's why we at Malta
have prepared these educational
materials for you to better understand
the seven defining attributes that make
you special in this chapter we focus on
perception it is the unfortunate truth
that when you go above ground you will
be faced with many post-nuclear
nuisances these frightening menaces will
come in all different shapes and sizes
and pose an immediate threat to your
survival you must learn to deal with
these dangers but may find this
challenging at first
that's why we've provided you with the
vault-tec assistance targeting system so
you can scan the threat and pinpoint
areas of weakness and the higher your
perception the more accurate you will be
why you'll put Davy Crockett to shame
there may be times when you must engage
in questionable activities
your perception can help keep you safe
during these morally ambiguous moments
practice your pilfering on youths the
elderly for the incapacitated
as you continue to purloin your way to
success try more challenging targets and
more skillful techniques for greater
returns don't get too cocky there sport
always look to sharpen your 5 senses
for perception doesn't stop there keenly
assessing the unfriendly locals and
terrain handling sensitive munitions
with blend building a long-distance
relationship regularly study your
vault-tec provided materials to prepare
for survival and to answer the question
do you know what makes you special